[thunder crashing]
She's handling like a sled.
What's the hell's
going on back there?
Just the cargo shifting,
Captain.
Check it out.
Yes, sir.
I'll check it out.
The hold-down straps are tight,
Captain.
[loud thud]
[thud]
Captain, I think there's
something moving around in here.
Lookit, Dave, I bleed easy.
Look inside that cargo.
[thudding continues]
What do you got?
I'm trying to get
the crate open, sir.
Sir, there are warning signs
all over this thing.
I don't think this is such
a good idea.
It's top secret,
but go ahead.
You got my permission.
Open it up.
[thunder crashes]
There ain't nothing
in here, sir.
-[snarling]
-Oh, my God.
-[pounding on crate]
-[screams]
Dave!
[creature snarling]
What the hell
is going on back there?
[Dave shouting indistinctly]
What the hell?
[creature roaring]
[console beeping rapidly]
-[inhuman roaring]
-[loud crashing]
[pilot]
No!
[explosion]
[water splashing]
[woman]
Oh, yeah.
Right there.
Oh, right there.
Robert, you...
What did you say?
Why did you stop?
You just called me Robert.
No, no, no. I said Roberta.
No, you said Robert.
There was no "ta"
at the end of it.
Roberta...
please excuse my improper
alliteration
in a moment of ecstasy.
I promise, next time
I will get your name right.
Look, I'm sorry.
I know that you see guys
sometimes.
I just hope
I'm the only girl you see.
You are the only girl
I see.
[both moan]
That feels good.
Oh, not so tight.
[laughs]
Not so tight.
What's too tight?
[snake moving]
[shrieks]
Jesus Christ,
you're scaring her.
Scaring her?
She's just giving you a hug.
Hi, baby.
I don't know why
you had to bring
that overgrown worm
with you anyway.
I hate that thing.
It could have bitten me!
Lady G is a python.
She doesn't bite,
she squeezes.
Besides, I can't leave her
at home alone.
Wherever I go, she goes.
Yeah.
-Where you going to go?
-I got to go take a leak.
[rustling]
[Roberta] Looks like
you've been up here before.
A few times.
-So, who's John?
-John? No.
You mean Joanna.
[lighter snaps]
Bitch.
What was that?
Nothing.
[rustling]
[hissing]
[screams]
Roberta?
This isn't funny!
[rustling]
-[hissing]
-Roberta?
Roberta?
Oh, God. Oh, God.
Oh, God.
No! No!
-[loud rustling]
-[sobbing]
[screams]
No! God, no!
No!
[screams]
[creature hissing]
* Mutual sight, mutual sound
* Mutual struggle
For shared ground *
* It's safe to say
They'll try to take from me *
* I'm just another one
For them to break down *
* Steeped in denial
The daily grind *
* Dream of a world for me
And my kind *
* It's safe
in the alternate reality *
* So stick your standards
Where the sun doesn't shine *
* They're for themselves *
* It doesn't matter
What they say *
* Promise the world
Then take it from you anyway *
* They'll break you down
Making your vision fade away *
* It's time to go
Get out of my space *
* Welcome to a world where
The air I breathe is mine *
* Nothing to overwhelm me
And nothing to cloud my mind *
* Be anyone, do anything
I'd ever want to try *
* Time doesn't exist here
I will never die *
* Explain the reasons
Explain the rhymes *
* It's not required
Inside our minds *
* It's safe to try
No need to justify *
* Or take their guilt trip
At the end of the line *
* They're for themselves *
* It doesn't matter
What they say *
* Promise the world
Then take it from you anyway *
* They'll break you down
Making your vision fade away *
* It's time to go
Get off of my case *
* Welcome to a world where
The air I breathe is mine *
* Nothing to overwhelm me
And nothing to cloud my mind *
* Be anyone, do anything
I'd ever want to try *
* Time doesn't exist here *
* Slip into a world where
The air I breathe is mine *
* Nothing to overwhelm me
And nothing to cloud my mind *
* Come with me into it
* And you know
What you will find *
* Time doesn't exist here
We will never die *
* Welcome to a world where
The air I breathe is mine *
* Nothing to overwhelm me
And nothing to cloud my mind *
* Be anyone, do anything
I'd ever want to try *
* Time doesn't exist here *
* Slip into a world where
The air I breathe is mine *
* Nothing to overwhelm me
And nothing to cloud my mind *
* Come with me into it...
Hey, Greg.
This isn't a racing circuit,
Cooper.
You keep riding
like that,
somebody's going to get hurt.
* They're for themselves *
* It doesn't matter
What they say *
* It's time to go
Get out of my face *
* Welcome to a world where
The air I breathe is mine *
* Nothing to overwhelm me
And nothing to cloud my mind *
* Be anyone, do anything
I'd ever want to try *
* Time doesn't exist here *
[metallic clanging]
-[alarm blares]
-Shit!
-[men laugh]
-Oh, pretty damn funny, huh?
[both]
Yep.
There she blows!
[cackles]
Are you guys
out of your minds?
Do you know what happens
when that goes past the red?
Hey, quit screwing around
in here!
For Christ's sake, Brian,
leave the door open.
We're dying in here.
Take it up with the city.
We leave the big door open,
we're going to get cited.
A $500-per-incident fine?
Brian, that door
is the only ventilation
we have in this place.
If you close that, we'll all
end up with brain damage.
You ain't gonna get
brain damaged.
Yeah, that's what you think.
You see those two vapor monkeys
over there?
Those two are permanently
defective.
I don't want
to end up like that,
or keeled over
with some dopey grin.
Like Dad?
The city will close us down
if we don't keep this place
buttoned up.
OSHA will shut us down
if we do.
That's the point.
They want to shut us down.
They're looking for an excuse.
Well, I'm not going to sit here
and let them
bury everything Dad spent
a lifetime building for us,
just so a bunch of snobs
can sit around
sipping lattes
and munching on biscotti.
Brian...
Dad died trying
to keep this place open.
I don't think that's what
he really wanted for us.
What do you know about what Dad
wanted?
You weren't even here.
[car horn honking]
That's Tommy. I got to go.
Well, then go.
Go ahead. Leave.
That's what you do best,
ain't it, John?
[rock music playing
on radio]
Hey, Johnny,
how you doing?
Great. Peachy.
Where are the girls?
They're going to meet us
at the lake.
[giggling]
[Kristin]
Do you love him?
[Theresa]
Oh, God, of course I do.
I've loved Tommy
ever since I first saw him
on the monkey bars
in second grade.
I've been in love with Theresa
since the time I saw her
in that tight varsity sweater
our freshman year.
So when do you think
he'll finally get around
to asking you
the question?
At the rate he's going?
Never.
I swear, all he ever
talks about is sex and...
Money.
These days
it is all about money.
-You don't care about money?
-Oh, heck, no.
I'd live in a trailer park
with Tommy if he'd ask me to.
But all he ever talks about
is this damn...
Kenny the Closer?
Kenny the Closer.
My God, the man's a legend.
He's an icon.
He's the number-one-selling
real estate agent
in the entire
southwestern corridor.
And there is no way that I'm
going to ask Theresa to marry me
until I'm pulling down bucks
like Kenny the Closer.
Come on, Theresa doesn't care
about your money. She loves you.
If that's the case,
how come she won't...?
You never slept
with Tommy?
Nope, not once.
Why not?
Well, we did come close
a couple times, but...
What if we get married,
and the first time we do it
it's like really bad sex?
Tommy, there's no such thing
as really bad sex.
[truck doors closing]
Hey.
How's your brother?
[scoffs]
Dying slowly
from toxic fumes.
Just doesn't know it yet.
You keep working there,
he'll be taking you with him.
-Hello.
That's what
you came back for?
Nah.
Not for that.
I never did thank you.
For what?
Wrecking your engagement
with Greg?
No.
From saving me
from a big mistake.
I like saving you.
-[water splashes]
-[Tommy] Come on, you weenies!
-Let's go!
-Tommy, you are so dead!
[Theresa]
Get in here.
[Theresa laughs]
[indistinct shouting]
[screams]
John!
-What happened?
-[Theresa] What?
Easy. It's okay.
It's all right. Hey.
Easy, girl. Easy.
[Kristin]
John...
-It's okay. It's okay.
-What are you doing?
[John laughs]
Easy, girl.
Oh, my God, that's Lady G.
-Who?
-[both] It's Lisa's.
-[car door closes]
-Okay.
I'm not even going to ask
how both of you know that.
What you got there,
Cooper?
That's Lisa's snake,
isn't it?
What are you doing here?
What, you think I came all
the way up here to spy on you?
Didn't you?
Guys, this is official.
A missing persons report.
Lisa didn't show up
at home this morning.
Well, she's a bit
on the wild side.
You'd know.
You used to date her.
Everybody used to date her.
[man, over radio]
Greg. Deputy Greg?
Deputy Greg, come in.
We found something.
-Let me take that.
-Please do.
God, you're such a girl.
How do you know Lisa?
Everybody knows Lisa.
-[flies buzzing]
-[police radio chatter]
So, what do you think?
I don't know
what to think.
what to think either.
You ever seen anything
like this before?
Never.
Neither have I.
Any idea what
might have caused it?
Nothing in my mind.
Nothing in my mind
either.
[car door opens and closes]
What you got, Griff?
[Griffin]
We think we found Lisa's body.
It's not pretty.
Oh, no.
Didn't you used
to date her?
Everybody used to date her.
Got to tell you, Griff,
whoever pulled this one
has a real mean streak.
She's burned to the bone.
Yeah, but with what?
I guess an acid.
Sulfuric, hydrochloric.
Battery.
I don't know.
[flies buzzing]
I won't know more
until I get her up on the table.
To tell you the truth...
this looks more like
an industrial accident
than a murder.
No, this was no accident.
You know, Rose and I saw Lisa
and that damn snake of hers
leave the diner last night
with Roberta Keeler.
Nobody's seen her
since either.
Well, all I know is,
burns like that don't happen
just going for a midnight swim.
What you got, Greg?
John Cooper.
Just ran into him
over at the watering hole.
He had Lisa's snake
with him.
He has been working
over at Perfecto
with his brother
since he got back.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
With all that acid.
What do you think, Griff?
Worth a little talk with him?
Oh, I don't know.
I mean, if that's Lisa,
where's Roberta?
I mean, is she missing?
Did she do this?
I guess it wouldn't hurt
to check and see
what John was up to
last night.
-Go ahead.
-Yes, sir.
I'll get an A.P.B. out
for Keeler too.
Good.
-This is great!
-What's great?
Well, we finally
get to grill that asshole
who stole your girl.
What do you mean,
"We get to grill"?
What, you're not going
to grill him?
I didn't say that.
I knew it. I knew it.
Good cop, bad cop.
And when we
are done with him,
he's going to be confessing
to the JFK hit.
When do we start?
I got it covered, Lou.
What are you talking about,
you got it covered?
What, you're not going
to let me help?
Come on, y-y-y-you got
to let me help.
Please, I promise,
I won't say a thing.
I'll be a fly on the wall.
I won't say anything
-Please, please?
-All right.
But you don't say one word.
-Not one word.
[Tommy]
Now listen to this.
I'm supposed to be showing
the Baxter place tomorrow.
Okay, two bedrooms,
two bathrooms.
Six percent of 150K,
I haven't even
run the comps yet.
Oh, shit!
What?
I was going to take
some Polaroids
to go with the comps,
and I left the damn camera
up at the Red Stone Estates.
No biggie. Just pick it up
after you drop me off.
I can't. I've got to get back
to the office.
Pick it up afterwards.
No, Theresa and I are going
to the show tonight.
If we don't get out by 5:00,
there's no way
we're going to make it.
Oh, I am so screwed.
[John]
I'll go get it for you.
-Would you?
-Yeah.
Thanks, man.
That's very cool.
[John]
No sweat.
[laughing]
Hey, hey, Tommy!
You going to close the deal
on that Baxter place tomorrow?
I hope so.
Hope? Hope is for losers, kid.
You got to know so.
Me, I'm showing Red Stone
tonight, model D.
Prospect is hot to trot!
You think I'm hoping?
Hell no!
You know what I'm--
Hey! Hey! You scratch it,
I'll hang your balls
like fuzzy dice from my mirror!
You got that, Billy?
You got it?
You piece of monkey shit!
Anyway, I'm going to ask you
one more time.
And this is Kenny the Closer
that's asking you.
Are you gonna
close that deal?
-Yeah.
-Are you gonna close that deal?
-Oh, yeah.
-Hell, yeah!
-That's the ticket!
Ka-ching, baby! Ha-ha!
[tires squeal
[horn honking]
[steam hissing]
What's going on?
Somebody done gone out
and got themselves murdered.
-Murdered?
-Yeah, Louis told us hisself.
Where? Here?
No, no, no,
up at the reservoir last night.
Lisa Johnson.
You know that's crazy.
Look, he may be
irresponsible,
but there's no way
that he would...
[John]
Hey.
Brian.
Why don't you
sit down for this?
It's all right.
I'd rather stand.
Where were you last night
between 10:00 and 12:00 p.m.?
You think I murdered Lisa?
Murdered?
Nobody said anything
about a murder.
What makes you think
there was a murder?
-Lenny and Boone told me.
-Oh, yeah?
And just how did they know?
They said you told them.
Oh, yeah.
I guess I did.
Louis, why don't you let John...
Yeah, yeah, yeah, fine.
But I'll be watching you,
mister.
So?
Come on, Greg.
Are you going to answer
the question?
Where were you last night?
I was at Kristin's place.
Is she willing
to confirm that?
Of course she would.
Here, ask her yourself.
You want me to dial?
I know the number.
Yes, my Liebchen.
[smacks lips]
Yes.
[clucks tongue]
Time to work.
Dr. Rudolph?
Yes.
Special Agent Parker
would like to see you now, sir.
What took you so long?
[laughs]
Ooh!
[laughing]
Oh, Mrs. Garibaldi.
You look absolutely
gorgeous today.
Francesca, please.
You're so sweet.
So, what have you got
for me today?
Something that will
excite me, I hope.
Follow me.
Use your imagination,
Mrs.--
I mean, Francesca.
That is such
a beautiful name.
Thank you.
My late husband
used to call me Fran.
Oh, can you believe it?
Oh, you are anything
but a Fran.
Imagine a cool winter night.
You and the one you love
staring into the flames.
[inhales]
Maybe a little incense.
Yeah.
-Candlelight.
-Ooh.
You make me want it
right now.
Let me show you
what I've got in the back.
I'd rather see
what you got in front.
[laughs]
Now, now, now, now.
The master suite.
Ooh.
[both giggle]
-Isn't it beautiful?
-Mm!
[laughs]
Just use your imagination.
Oh, I am.
[laughs]
And now...
my very favorite room
in Red Stone Estates.
[giggles]
[chuckles]
Oh!
Floating camellias.
Mm!
Shall I?
Please do.
[motor whirring]
[man screaming on recording]
[static crackles on recording]
[tape turned off]
What the hell
have you gotten us into?
This is horrible.
Such a loss.
You knew those men?
No, no, no, not the men.
The specimen.
You can always get more men,
but...
but the specimen...
the specimen
is irreplaceable.
What exactly do you do,
Doctor?
I'm a herpetologist.
So you specialize in reptiles.
Mm-hm.
Is that was Biogene
was transporting?
Not in the traditional sense,
no.
What, um...
What we had
was something unique.
An evolutionary chimera
of immense physiological scale.
Something with unparalleled
abilities and characteristics.
A hybrid, if you will,
integrated from a variety
of distinct serpentine species.
You hide behind
a lot of big words, Doctor,
but what you just said
still doesn't tell us
what we need to know.
We know the flight originated
in Southeast Asia.
The authorization came
from the State Department
for the use of a transport
out of Guam.
But nowhere in the manifest
is there so much as a mention
of exactly what it was
you were transporting.
So I'm asking you, Doctor,
in simple laymen's terms...
what was it?
Well, in simple
laymen's terms...
a very big snake.
[Francesca]
Oh! Oh, my God, it's huge!
It's... It's enormous!
I just can't handle it!
It's too much!
[Kenny] Yes, you can.
You can do it, baby.
I know you can.
Thirty percent down,
8.9% financing
for the first two years.
You can do it, baby!
Oh, it's just so much more
than I expected.
Isn't there anything I can do
to get you to go down?
All right.
Twenty percent down,
8.5% financing
with a ballooning
mortgage to 12.9.
And that's the best deal you're
going to get from anybody.
-[glass shatters]
-What was that?
Sounded like the garage.
[loud crash]
Damn kids are after my car!
Wait here!
All right, 15% down,
7.5% financing,
with a ballooning
mortgage to 12.9%.
That's the best you're gonna get
from anybody. Think about it!
Don't sign with anybody
until I get back!
Ka-ching, baby!
[loud crashing]
[loud crashing continuous]
[snickers]
Oh, yes.
Hyah!
No!
Billy!
You little shit!
Billy?
You little creep!
Your ass is mine now!
[footsteps]
[footsteps continuous]
[objects clatter]
[thumping]
[laughs]
[yells]
What the...?
Huh. Hm.
[hissing]
[hisses]
[coughs]
[screams]
[hissing and snarling]
[squeals]
[gasping]
[yelping]
[Kenny screaming]
[snake squealing]
Yes, hello,
I'm at the Red Rock Estates.
I don't know,
just send a car or a truck.
No, I don't know the address.
It's the big one.
Listen, you little idiot,
just send a car or something.
Jesus Christ, you are 911.
[snake roaring]
[Kenny screaming]
[shrieks]
[whimpering]
[both scream]
Oh, my...
-[garage door motor whirring]
-[cackling]
[screams]
Oh, no!
No! No!
No! No! No!
[roars]
Hello?
Anybody here?
Kenny?
Cool.
[objects clattering]
Kenny?
[clatter continuous]
Hello?
[dragging and thudding]
Why would Biogene
want a giant snake?
[sighs]
Calling it a snake
misses the point.
As I said, it was unique.
Just the study
of how it projects
its corrosive
digestive fluids
could prove invaluable
for military applications.
This thing pukes acid?
Well, you could put it that way,
yes.
What it actually does is
to draw up its stomach acid
into sacs located here.
Once there, it contracts those
sacs with powerful muscles,
which allow it to shoot
this highly caustic acid
with incredible force,
much like a cobra
spits its venom
to subdue its prey.
Look at these.
The cockpit hatch
was torn open wide enough
to birth a whale through.
[Rudolph]
Yes, its size and strength
were impressive,
but now your people
have managed to kill it.
Maybe not.
Looks like your pet might have
some life left in him.
What?
There were no remains found
in the wreckage,
human or otherwise.
It would only have eaten those
men if they were still alive.
Are you saying this thing
ate the crew
and survived
the plane crash?
Yes, it's possible.
But if it's still alive,
then we have a chance
to capture it and perhaps...
Kill it.
Agent Parker,
this specimen
is a biological gold mine.
The DNA alone
is worth millions.
You can scrape your DNA
off whatever's left.
We've already lost
an entire flight crew,
and by now we may even have
collateral losses.
[scoffs]
Collateral losses?
That's a rather antiseptic
way of describing death,
don't you think?
Keep it small.
I want this thing solved
before anyone even knows
there was a problem.
I'm on it.
You have no idea
what you're up against.
You don't know my men.
[sighs]
This is not some garden snake
you're going after.
We are talking about
a perfect killing machine.
A 129-foot
all-terrain vehicle
capable of speeds
exceeding 50 miles an hour,
with skin that can deflect
an anti-tank round,
enhanced night vision,
and a voracious appetite
for human flesh.
It will slaughter your men
before they have a chance
to blink.
I don't know what it was.
Some kind of big animal.
I think it had a tail
or something.
And scales.
Scales?
I don't know, I just couldn't
get a good look at it.
It moved so quick.
-What about the bones?
-Bones?
The bones,
the ones in the garage?
Yeah, Cooper, you give old Kenny
a little acid bath?
I don't know anything
about bones.
Stripped him clean,
hacked that woman's head off
with a butcher knife?
-Ease up, Lou.
-Ease up, my ass.
[stammers]
Greg found him red-handed
with the murder weapon.
That wasn't a murder weapon.
Knife ain't got
a drop of blood on it.
Oh, come on, he could have
wiped it clean.
It had to be a big blade.
A machete.
Took her head off
in one clean shot.
What about the blood?
If Cooper did it,
he'd be soaked in it.
Come on, come on,
you guys aren't telling me
you're buying that crap
about a big snake, are you?
No. Hell, no.
Besides, we haven't
found Roberta.
And for my money,
she's still a suspect.
Well, now, Lou does have
a point there, Griff.
I mean, the bones.
The only thing could have
washed them that clean is acid,
and the only place
in this town
with that kind of acid
is their shop.
Cooper.
Yeah?
[Griffin]
You don't have any plans to
leave town this weekend, do you?
I've been dying
to use this stuff.
I bet we could do that.
Well, maybe it just
looks easy.
Good point.
I wish I had somewhere else
to look,
but right now I got
only one fact to work with.
There's not a whole lot
of places in this town where a--
where a body can be stripped
to its bones.
I can't afford
to be shut down.
I can appreciate that,
Brian,
but I don't see any other way
to handle this.
My brother's not a murderer.
What's going on?
We're shutting you down,
Cooper.
-Greg...
-Take it up with the sheriff.
Come on, Griff,
give us a break here.
I have only one break to offer,
and it ain't much.
Maybe, just maybe, you won't
have to empty the tanks.
Brian, I'm...
Sorry?
Hell, congratulations, John.
You've managed to do
what no one else could:
close the doors forever
on Perfecto Plating.
-This isn't my fault, Brian.
-Well, whose fault is it, John?
Mine?
Fine. I quit.
Hey, don't bother!
You're fired!
-[tires screech]
-Oh!
[groans]
[panting]
Oh, no, my bike.
Oh, this is great.
This is just fucking great.
Is there anything else
you can do to ruin my life?
-Don't push it.
-Don't tell me not to push it.
You take away my job.
You ruin my bike.
You steal my girl when I'm gone
for two seconds.
-You're fucking ruining my life!
-Your life?
I'm ruining your life?
Fuck you!
I was set to be married,
have a house and a family.
My life was planned out
until you came back.
She never loved you.
You were just a shoulder
to cry on.
Oh, is that right?
Maybe she did love me
before you started banging her
behind my back.
[grunts]
Take it off, Deputy.
Without the badge and the gun,
it's just you and me.
This isn't the schoolyard,
you know.
I heard that.
[yelling]
-You're dead.
-Yeah, so are you.
I didn't steal Kristin.
No, you just banged her.
[both yell]
[both panting]
You fight like a girl,
you wuss.
You're a sissy.
Coward.
Dickwad.
You okay, Deputy Greg?
Yeah, everything's fine.
Go back and play, kids.
Everything's fine.
Go on.
[chuckles]
You're a pain in the ass,
you know that?
[both laugh]
Forget about it, man.
It's totaled.
I'll buy you a new one.
You don't get it,
do you?
You can't buy me
another one of these.
Why not?
It's just a bike.
How much can it cost?
2,400 bucks.
But that's not the point.
This bike got me
out of this dust hole, man.
It's irreplaceable.
Sorry, man.
I had no idea.
Yeah.
This sponsor gave me
this prototype, right?
State-of-the-art stuff.
Shimano brakes,
grip shifts, RockShox.
You know what I did with it?
I gave it to Tommy.
-You gave it to Tommy?
-Yup.
I gave that bike to Tommy,
because this is the bike
that mattered to me the most.
This is the bike that gave me
what I thought I wanted.
You know what I got at home,
bottom right drawer?
Application to Quantico.
FBI?
Filled it out four and a half
years ago, never sent it in.
-Why not?
-Yeah, right.
Some hick cop thinking
he can play Eliot Ness?
-It's dumb.
-Please.
It can't be dumber
than some hick punk
thinking he could ride pro.
Yeah, but you did it.
You got out of here.
[police siren blurts]
[car approaching]
Deputy, you're not
answering your radio.
Hikers on a bike path
found another body.
Sheriff Wade's already up there.
Come on, let's roll.
Let's roll.
[loud crash]
[flies buzzing]
Any luck on those bones
we found in the garage?
Checking the dental records
with Hank.
I'm hoping he can get a match
with one of his patients.
What in the hell
could do this?
I don't know.
It's weird, very weird.
Well, it's the same type
of acid death we saw earlier.
Acid. Acid.
Do I have to say it again?
John Cooper, acid.
What's his motive?
Yeah, and where's
Roberta Keeler?
[sighs]
Don't need dental records
on this one.
Yeah. Only guy in town's
got a fancy watch like that
is Kenny Summers.
-It's a fake.
-So was Kenny.
[sighs]
[inaudible]
[cell phone rings]
Hey, Greg,
a little help here.
Floyd's phone.
[sighs]
Thank you.
Hey, why are you
defending him?
That asshole's probably
boning your ex-bitch right now.
Don't ever talk about her
like that.
-Do you hear me?
-Yeah, I'm sorry.
-Never talk about her like that.
-I'm sorry.
Hey, guys,
give it a rest.
That was Hank.
They made a positive ID
on the bones from the garage.
It was Roberta Keeler.
Okay, Louis,
you get your wish.
You guys bring in John Cooper.
Meet me back at the office.
See? See, Sheriff?
I'm a thinker.
You know what I mean?
[Greg]
Have fun, Floyd.
Thanks.
We're going to try
the campground
up at Crystal Lake.
And if it's full then,
I don't know,
we'll play it by ear.
Where's John?
We should get going.
What happened?
Nothing.
Greg and I just got
in a little scuffle.
-Greg did this to you?
-Well, Greg, we just sort of...
Oh, man.
How's it going, Louis?
I'd love to tell you
about my emotional and physical
well-being, Theresa,
but I've got some unfortunate
business to attend to.
Excuse me.
This might get ugly.
John Cooper,
you are under arrest.
Now extend your hands.
I will frisk you
downtown.
-[car approaches]
-Extend your hands!
You got to be kidding me.
No, no, no.
I'm not kidding.
We found Bobbie Keeler,
Mr. Murderer.
Mr. Killer.
Mr. Acid-Dipper of the Skin--
Louis, what the hell
are you doing?
I am apprehending
the suspect, Deputy.
Give me the gun.
-Pardon me?
-Hand it over.
Now, walk to your car,
open the back door
and put the suspect
in the back seat.
What about the handcuffs?
Everybody okay?
You all right?
You bastard.
How could you do that to him?
Can I talk to you
for a minute?
Oh, I'd love to hear
what you have to say.
Kristin...
You probably hate him.
You probably hate me too.
That does not give you the right
to abuse your authority
-and have him arrested.
-I just wanted--
I'm the one that left you.
Don't take it out on him.
-It is not his fault.
-That's fine.
Am I supposed to move away
from Ruby?
You want to drive me
from my hometown?
-Are you done?
-No.
You guys used to be friends.
Why don't you have it out
with each other and settle it?
-We did.
-Because I'm not going to...
What?
I don't think John did it.
And I'm going to prove it.
Let me see
if I got this straight.
You boys--what department
did you say you were from again?
-NSA.
-Okay.
So you got this...
An operative.
Yeah, an operative.
This real Rambo type.
This guy makes Rambo
look like Richard Simmons.
Uh-huh, and you've had
this man
locked up in a cage
since 1974?
In a metal box.
In a metal box
in a military psychiatric unit.
And somehow he escaped,
and he's the one that done
all these murders?
That's about the size of it.
Any questions?
Just one.
Do you expect me to believe
this load of horseshit?
Let me put it this way,
Sheriff.
It would be highly expedient
if you would believe
this horseshit.
[Griffin]
Whoo!
These cuffs are too tight.
Oh, yeah? Well, you're going
to have to get used to it.
-Better?
-Yeah. Thanks.
Ahem. Deputy.
What the hell are you doing?
You know how this works.
-Good cop, bad cop.
-Oh, right.
Tell you what.
Why don't you be the bad cop
for a change?
For real?
You don't mind?
I mean, this isn't some pothead.
This is a real,
live murder suspect.
No, I've...
had my fill of being bad cop.
Louis, doesn't Wade
keep a gun
in the bottom right drawer
in there?
-The suspect.
-Mm-hm.
Didn't think to check
in the desk drawers, did you?
-No.
-[Louis] Oh, that's right.
Play innocent.
Put this in evidence, Deputy.
It's not my gun.
I didn't even touch it.
-He's right, Lou.
-Yeah. Technicalities.
Always the dad-burn
technicalities!
Killers screaming
for their rights.
But what about
the victims' rights, mister?
What about the victims?
Want to call a lawyer?
Yeah, that's the ticket.
Hide behind some cap-toothed
F. Lee Cochran-type sharpie.
[sniffs]
But that's not going to help
your sorry ass, boy.
No, sir. Not in Ruby.
No, sir.
You want to know why?
Do you want to know?
[inhales and exhales sharply]
Because I am the law here.
-Cut him loose.
-Sheriff?
You heard me,
Mr. "I Am the Law."
Sorry for any
inconvenience, John.
Does this mean...
Can I leave town now?
Because I had plans.
Yeah, yeah. Fine.
Just be on your way now.
[Greg]
Have a good time.
Say hey to Kristin for me.
Yeah, I'll do that.
What is this place?
It's an emergency
water treatment facility,
fully automated.
The Army Corps of Engineers
built it underground
so it'd be secure,
even in the event
of a nuclear war.
It'll keep your snake out.
Here's the crash site.
Our position is here.
Bodies have been found here,
here and here.
This, we believe,
is our target.
You don't have enough men.
That's not your concern.
This team will do
what they were trained for.
After that, I don't care
if you carve up the carcass
and open up a rib joint.
Bottom line:
This thing dies today.
You don't seem to realize
the opportunity
you're wasting here.
Consider the potential
for weapons research.
New neurotoxins.
Antidotes for those created
by your enemies.
Intriguing, Mr. Parker?
I'm not as mercenary
as you may think, Doctor.
I am concerned
with the loss of life.
Now, I didn't know
that flight crew,
but once I signed on
to this little scheme of yours,
they became my men.
No one else dies
because of this thing.
Do you understand that?
Oh, yes, I understand.
I just hope
your snake here does.
The satellite passes over
only once every three hours.
The next pass is in 72 minutes
from now.
When that occurs,
I want us to be in position.
Once we have confirmed location
of the target,
we'll take it out.
I want this thing nailed
before dark.
Excuse me.
What's this here?
This red line?
No. Radar echo.
Local law enforcement
has established roadblocks
at all major access points
on our perimeter.
Dootsen will coordinate
operations from here.
I will be leading Alpha team
down this approach.
Bravo team,
you'll flank the perimeter.
Stay in contact.
Once we have a lock,
we'll dig in and start shelling
the hell out of this thing.
When we have a confirmed kill,
we'll go in and mop up.
[Dootsen, over radio]
Stand by, everyone.
Bird's in position,
downloading.
[beeping]
Dootsen, status.
Target appears stationary
at the original coordinates.
Same as before.
It hasn't moved
in three hours.
That seem right to you?
Well, it's consumed
a great deal lately,
far exceeding
its normal diet.
It's possible that
the high-caloric intake
has induced a respite
in its metabolic activities.
Meaning?
It's having
a little siesta.
Let me know
when you have a visual.
I've got him, sir.
Visual confirmation a quarter
klick southwest of my position.
Right where the bird
showed it would be.
All units, lock and prepare
to open fire on my command.
It's time to put
your baby to bed.
Bravo unit ready.
Tactical confirming.
Both units show in position
and ready.
Take her out.
[gunfire]
Sounds like a damn war
in there.
Boys will be boys.
Sir, you want to go in?
[chuckles]
Louis.
[beeping]
[gunfire continues]
Cease fire.
Cease fire! Cease fire!
Target destroyed, sir.
No movement.
I repeat, no movement.
You're confirmed.
All units, move in.
Break out your petri dishes,
Doc.
Time to clean up.
[computer beeping]
All right, everyone,
let's move out.
We got work to do.
Kill confirmed.
Target destroyed.
We blew the guts
out of it, sir.
[flies buzzing]
It shed its skin.
You knew this.
You knew it was molting.
No, no, no, I didn't.
No, I didn't. I-I-I swear.
[cocks gun]
I should turn you
into snake bait.
What happened?
[Parker]
It was a setup.
The snake shed its skin,
and the doctor knew it.
No, I didn't know.
I suspected, based on
the surveillance photos,
but I couldn't be certain.
But, sir, it was here.
I saw it move.
We were decoyed.
[Rudolph]
I warned you it was intelligent.
I told you, this isn't just
some common snake.
Well, if it was here...
then where is it now?
[snake roars]
Fan out! Take cover!
Protect yourselves!
Wait!
[Parker]
What?
[whispering]
Don't move.
Trust me.
Stay completely still.
[hisses]
Don't.
[gun cocks]
-[snake roars]
-[gunshot]
[groaning weakly]
[breathing heavily]
* I met my lover
At a restaurant *
* She took my order
With a big smile *
-[Tommy laughing]
-I liked the other one better.
Yeah, it plays better
in black and white.
-Totally.
-Hey, where's your mom?
[door closes]
Mom?
I cut her up into tiny pieces
and I stuffed her in the freezer
in the basement!
[laughs]
Seriously, where is she?
She's visiting her sister
in Walla Walla for the weekend.
Really?
Oh.
Yeah.
So we have this place
just to ourselves?
Uh-huh.
So it's, like...
just you and me?
Uh-huh.
Just us?
So it's like...
It's just Tommy
and Theresa tonight?
Uh-huh.
[cat screams]
Jesus! What got into Caesar?
-God.
-[sighs]
[door opens]
You know where the couch is.
Make yourself comfy.
The shower upstairs is broken,
so use the one downstairs.
But I'll be there
in the morning,
so don't think about
checking out the goods.
-But...
-I told John and Kristin
that we'd pick them up
at 6:00 a.m.,
so I'd get some rest,
because 5:00 a.m.
comes around really early.
Don't let the bedbugs bite.
[scoffs]
Bedbugs?
Dude.
Come on, Greg, I'm tired.
I want to go home.
What happened to all that,
"Let's go get the bad guys"?
Okay, okay.
So I've learned my lesson,
all right?
Which is?
[Louis]
I've got to be patient.
I've got to let the evidence
come to me.
[Greg]
That's right.
Now, try to get some sleep. I'll
see you in the morning.
See you in the morning.
[alarm beeping]
[turns off alarm]
Wake up.
Showtime.
Hey.
I'm up, I'm up.
Jeez.
[rock music plays]
[hissing]
[rock music playing continuous]
[glass shatters]
Tommy, is that you?
[loud crash]
[hissing]
All right.
I'm up, I'm up.
Dude. Jeez.
[urinating]
[hissing]
[groaning]
[gasps]
Damn it, Tommy.
Couldn't you have at least
waited a minute?
[screams]
[zipper rasps]
Ah!
[shrieking]
Theresa?
Tommy!
Theresa!
-Theresa!
-Tommy!
Tommy!
-[pounding on door]
-Theresa, open the door!
[grunts]
[roars]
[whimpers]
Open up the door, Theresa!
Tommy!
[hissing]
[yelling]
[squeaks]
-[snarls]
-[Theresa yells]
[sobbing]
Tommy!
No. No.
-Tommy!
-Open up!
[yells]
The door's stuck, honey!
Tommy, get away
from that thing!
-What? What?
-Get away from the door.
There's a snake.
-Oh.
-In the basement.
Tommy, get away from the door!
Dude, you got me out of bed
for a snake?
-[grunts]
-Tommy!
[screams]
No!
[crying]
Tommy!
[engine starts]
Come on, come on! Move!
[hissing]
[phone line ringing]
No answer.
Maybe we should
go over there.
[snake roars]
Oh, God. Come on.
Move! Move!
[screams]
[gasps and grunts]
[roars]
[sobs]
[snake roaring distantly]
[panting]
-[hissing]
-Ah!
[thud]
-[thud]
-[sobbing]
[roaring]
[screams]
Oh, my God.
That's Tommy's.
[turns ignition off]
Wait here.
They're not in here.
Theresa!
Tommy!
[honks horn]
-[hissing]
-[Kristin] Theresa!
-[snarling]
-[car horn honks]
Theresa?
Tommy?
[honking horn]
Theresa! Tommy?
John! Kristin!
[honking horn]
[snake hissing]
John!
Kristin!
[whimpers]
-[roars]
-[Kristin screams]
Get out.
[snake roaring]
[Kristin]
Go! Go!
Quick!
[police radio squawking]
[clears throat]
Hey, Griff, any word yet?
Oh...
[sighs]
Not a peep.
You heard any more fireworks?
Negative.
Maybe you should
check on them.
Yeah, maybe I should.
I'll wake Louis up.
Wake up, sleepyhead.
Time to catch bad guys.
[static crackles]
Louis?
If you're not up
when I get over there,
I'm going to kick your ass.
Hey, what is that?
[John]
I don't know.
Come on.
Hey, slow down.
Forget that.
It looks clear.
What is this place?
I don't know.
[Rudolph]
No!
Did you hear that?
-Oh, yeah.
-[Rudolph] No!
Stupid.
So blind.
Wrong.
Blind.
[sobbing]
Who the hell is he?
[Rudolph crying]
Hello?
Sir?
Already I had fixed
my gaze upon him.
And he rose upright,
with breast in countenance,
as if he entertained
some great scorn of hell.
Python.
He's in shock.
So blind.
So wrong.
Not until I stared
in its eyes...
and saw the terror around me.
Not until then did I...
Did I realize
what I'd done.
[leaves rustling]
Maybe it evolved naturally.
Maybe it's been out there
all along
and we just never knew it.
Perhaps it's some kind
of mutation.
We certainly dumped enough
Agent Orange on Southeast Asia
during the war.
But if it has
all these features
from all different kinds
of snakes like you say it does,
it couldn't have
evolved naturally.
Yeah, but maybe it didn't.
Maybe it was created
in some kind
of secret government
operation.
What? I've seen it
a hundred times in the movies.
They're always doing stuff
like that, right?
Well, actually,
he's correct.
We considered the possibility
ourselves.
We just never knew.
That's why we were so eager
to get it back to the lab
to examine it.
[door slams]
Did we forget
to lock the door?
Lock it?
We didn't even close it.
Shit!
[thumping]
-Theresa!
-[gasps]
What's with the towel?
It got Tommy.
[crying]
[turns ignition off]
What the hell are you doing?
[gun cocks]
Louis?
Look at all this stuff.
Are you telling me you couldn't
take it out with all this?
They never had a chance.
They emptied their entire
arsenal at a shed skin.
There's no way the snake
could take this much heat.
If you could hit it.
What if we lured it down here?
What, are you out
of your mind?
Look, let's just wait it out.
Sooner or later, it's bound
to get hungry and move on.
[Rudolph]
You must understand,
it's still basically a snake.
Even at its size,
it could go a month
without feeding
right outside that door.
There's not enough food in here
for us to wait that long.
And if it did decide to leave,
where do you think it would go?
Ruby.
Oh, my God. The whole town is
like an all-you-can-eat special.
And I don't want to wait around
to see what's going to happen.
So, what do you say?
How about it?
Well, I say we kill
the motherfucker.
Sheriff Wade.
Come on, Griff.
[Kristin, over radio]
Greg, can you hear me?
-Kristin, is that you?
-[Kristin] Greg?
Kristin, what are you doing
on this channel?
[Kristin]
Greg, we need your help.
Listen...
[hissing]
[John]
Wish me luck, baby.
Here.
Set.
[radio beeps]
Armed.
Okay, let's go, let's go,
let's go.
[beeping]
[hissing]
[grunting and panting]
[snake squealing distantly]
[gasps]
[panting]
[hissing]
[snake snarling]
I'm coming through.
Get ready.
-[loud crash]
-[all gasp]
Well, that's not going
to hold for long.
No, it won't, so come on.
Get going, get going, get going!
-Go, go, go.
-[John] Get Kristin!
-[Kristin] Right on!
-[Rudolph] All right!
[loud banging]
[panting]
Go.
[snake squealing distantly]
[hissing]
[grunts]
[distant roaring]
Greg!
Come on, come on.
I got to tie this to the bumper!
Greg, where's the bumper?
-There's no bumper!
-The chassis. Get under there.
The chassis,
right under there.
[faint roaring]
Now.
I'm trying.
I think it's there.
-Now, guys.
-Go, Greg! Go! Go!
Come on!
Now's the time!
[Kristin]
John!
John, are you okay?
[John]
That hurt.
[snake roaring]
[Greg]
Nice job, John.
[Kristin]
Let's go, let's go!
Move it!
[tires squeal]
[hissing]
[police radio squawking]
Miss, I think
you've earned this.
Thanks.
This is for you, Tommy.
-[button clicks]
-[remote beeps rapidly]
Somehow, I thought
it would be bigger.
What happened?
Python must have torn out
the antenna leads
when he crashed through
the bunker.
So, what do we do?
We have to reset
the detonator.
Here.
Would you please take her?
Take good care of her for me.
She's all I've got.
What are you talking about?
Redemption.
Where's he going?
Doc, don't go in there!
-[stammers]
-John!
-Okay, could--oh, yeah.
-Oh, nice.
Sit tight.
Could you take this?
You've got to be kidding me.
-John, come on.
-Shit!
He's all alone with that snake,
Kristin.
-Come on! It's going to blow!
-[Greg] John!
[bomb beeping]
[beeping stops]
[Rudolph gasps]
[breathing heavily]
[snake hissing]
Take the snake. Take the snake.
[Greg]
Come on.
[hissing]
[snake roars]
[indistinct police
radio chatter]
[coughing]
-Good work.
-[laughs]
[snake roars]
[John] Get in the car! What kind
of Wheaties does this thing eat?
[tires squeal]
All right, plan B.
Now, this thing survived a plane
crash and major explosives.
It won't burn.
Can't shoot it.
Any suggestions?
The plating plant.
The acid.
Think we could dump this thing
in one of those tanks of yours?
Got any eights?
Go fish.
Do you even know
how to play this game?
Go fish.
[groans]
-What the hell are you doing?
-No time to explain, Bri.
But let's just say
there's this little...
-[all] Little?
-Big. Big thing after us.
Well, actually,
it's after the whole town.
-What are you talking about?
-[snake roars distantly]
That.
-[all scream]
-Come on, come on, come on!
What is that thing?
Show them where
the winch controls are.
-What for?
-Just show me!
Go, go, go, go!
-I'll bring it to you.
-No.
You risked your life last time.
I'll do it.
Nah, it's okay. I'm getting
the hang of this thing now.
All's I got to do is get
its attention first, like this.
Got your attention?
[roars]
Go, go!
The controls
are right there.
-Grab that.
-What do we do?
Get a wrench. Get a wrench.
Okay.
[machinery whirring]
[panting]
[exhales]
[Brian]
Hurry up, hurry up.
[whispers]
Come on.
[snake hissing]
[roars]
[John grunts]
It's good.
-Hit it!
-Okay!
[machinery whirring]
Let's go.
[snake roaring]
[gasps]
[panting and grunting]
Hyah!
[roars]
[panting]
Psst, hey.
Where is it?
[roars]
-What happened?
-Like you said,
I got his attention.
[both scream]
[panting]
[snarls]
[liquid bubbling]
Ah!
[grunting]
[squeals]
[grunts]
[roars]
[roaring]
[shrieking]
[breathing heavily]
* I can change the world
Yeah *
* Yeah
* I can change the world
Ha!
Checkmate,
you sorry son of a bitch.
You used the Spassky maneuver
at the end there.
Well, next time I'll be prepared
and use the Fischer countermove.
Very well.
Jeez, you guys, what's it been?
Like, six hours?
Get a life.
If you're looking for a bike
with tight handling
and high speed,
especially when being hunted
by a giant reptile
with bad breath,
this is the one for you.
From now on...
you can call me
Special Agent Larson.
-You got in?
-I got in.
Great!
The FBI's going to be proud
to have you.
Maybe helping kill a giant
acid-spitting snake
pulled some strings
with the boys out at Quantico.
We're going to miss you
down here.
Yeah, I'm going
to miss you guys too.
I think it's time
I went out in the world
and tried to figure out
some of the things you did.
Besides, it's getting
a little crowded around here.
Tell me about it. We've been
swamped since opening day.
A man in your--whoo, condition
should not be drinking.
Congratulations, stud boy.
What?
We're pregnant.
I'm going to have a baby.
I'm going to have a baby!
[giggles]
[both laugh]
* 'Cause I can change
The world *
* Yeah
* I can change the world
Yeah *
* Yeah, I can change the world
* Yeah
* I can change the world
* World, yeah
["Carry Me" by William L. Smith
playing]
* She don't like me
Thinking that *
* I can do the way I do
* She don't like
To make up her mind *
* She wants what's best
For you *
* Time goes by
* Now I find I ain't got
That much to say *
* I'm inclined
To spit it out *
* Never take my love away
* Carry me
* Walk beside me
While we grow old *
* Bless my soul
And always carry me *
* If you still need a reason
* Or just an easy way out
* With not much left
To believe in *
* I wonder what
All the talk's about *
* Whoa-oh-oh-oh
* Whoa
* Carry me
* Walk beside me
While we grow old *
* Bless my soul
And always carry me *
* Carry me, carry me
* Carry me
* Walk beside me
While we grow old *
* Bless my soul
And always carry me *